UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Excavation site images, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004; 7.45 Linear Feet; 1424 Digital Object(s)
  - 2CC78, 1978 -- 1979; MS210.004.004
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019 (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020 (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00020.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021 (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 15KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00021.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022 (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 16KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00022.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023 (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00023.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024 (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 17KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00024.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025 (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00025.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026 (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 18KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00026.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027 (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 19KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00027.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028 (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00028.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029 (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 20KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00029.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030 (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 22KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00030.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031 (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00031.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032 (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 23KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00032.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033 (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00033.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034 (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 24KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00034.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00035 (Box 2)